Anne Hampton Brewster papers LCP.Brewster
Library Company of Philadelphia
- Series XI. Autograph collection
  - Lock of hair of Washington, George, undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence to Potter, Brigadier General to Washington, George, 1777 October 15 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lock of hair of Jefferson, Thomas, circa 1826 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence from Jefferson, Thomas to Randolph, Martha, 1792 December 6 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence from Monroe, James to Trist, Nicholas Philip, 1827 August 23 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence from Madison, James to Trist, Nicholas Philip, 1827 November 3 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Visiting card of Audenried, Joseph C., undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Autograph of Sherman, William Tecumseh, 1872 February 19 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Autograph of Sheridan, Philip H. (with pressed plant and visiting card) and autograph of Forsyth, James W. (with visiting card), 1871 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Continental currency, 1777 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Confederate currency, 1864 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Book plate of Washington, George, circa 1780 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Stamps of the Confederate states, circa 1865 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper clippings about Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation, 1864 May 18 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Newspaper clippings about Lincoln's Emancipation Proclamation, 1862 July 17 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Autograph album, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Series XII. Mary Howell collection of correspondence with Anne Hampton Brewster
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1854 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1855 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1855-1856 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1857-1858 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1858-1859 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1860 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1861-1862 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1863 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, circa 1863-1865 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1864 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1865 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1866 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1867 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1868 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary from Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1874 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Letters to Howell, Mary: Book review by Brewster, Anne Hampton, 1868 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Letter to Howell, Mary and original manuscript label "Notes and letters from my dearest Anne Brewster", undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Letter to Howell, Mary from Daniels, C.J., 1861 November 8 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Series XIII. Carpenter correspondence
  - Carpenter correspondence: Carpenter, Harriet Odin Dorr to Carpenter, James Edward, 1872, 1886 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Carpenter correspondence: Carpenter, Louis H. to Carpenter, Harriet Odin Dorr, 1888 September 27 (Box 28, Folder 9)